welcome back to another audacity
欢迎回到另一个大胆的地方
tutorial in this video I'll show you how
教程在本视频中 我将向您展示如何
to remove background noise from your
要删除背景噪音 请执行以下操作
audio recording or from a music file and
音频记录或从音乐文件和
so I'm just going to play this I've
所以我要播放这个我已经
created a sample file for you to listen
创建了一个示例文件以供您收听
to that we can work off of so I'm going
我们可以解决的 所以我要走了
to play it and you'll see what I mean so
演奏它 你就会明白我的意思
you see we get all this noise if I left
你看 如果我走了 我们会听到这么多噪音
click and select this we can play just
点击并选择这个 我们可以只玩
some here kind of this background noise
这里的一些背景噪音
that's just kind of constant so this is
这只是一种常量 所以这是
what we want to get rid of so luckily
我们这么幸运地想摆脱的是什么
there's an effect in audacity to do this
大胆地这样做是有影响的
so we go to effects and it's called
所以我们去找特效 这叫做
noise reduction so if we go to noise
减少噪音 所以如果我们去噪音
reduction without having anything
没有任何东西就减少了
selected we go to effect and we go to
选定的我们将生效 然后我们将
noise reduction we see it says you need
降噪我们看到了 它说你需要
to select some audio so you might think
选择一些音频 这样你可能会认为
at first well let's just select
首先 让我们只选择
everything ctrl a this is not the way to
一切都按Ctra键这不是通向
do it by the way I'm just showing you
顺便说一句 我只是向你展示一下
what you might intuitively try and do
你直觉上可能会尝试和做的事情
you go to noise reduction and we see
你去降噪 我们会看到
there's actually different steps we have
实际上我们有不同的步骤
step 1 and step 2 so step one says
第一步和第二步所以第一步说
select a few seconds of just noise so
只选择几秒钟的噪音 这样
I'd acid he knows what to filter out and
我认为他知道要过滤掉什么
then click get profile noise so we don't
然后点击获取配置文件噪音 这样我们就不会
want to click this right now because
我现在就想点击它 因为
otherwise it'll select the entire audio
否则 它将选择整个音频
as it'll think that's the noise so
因为它会认为那是噪音 所以
instead what we want to do is just
相反 我们想要做的只是
select a part that we know is noise so
选择一个我们知道是噪波的部分
we'll and the longer the better on this
我们会做得越久越好
so we'll just click play so that's some
我们只需点击播放 这样就可以了
good noise there wasn't click in there I
很好的噪音 里面没有滴答声
don't know if that will affect us or not
不知道这会不会影响我们
or we could try this one at the end
或者我们可以在最后试一试这个
maybe it's better good that's just
也许这样更好 那只是
constant good noise so then we go back
持续不断的好噪音 然后我们就回去
to effects and we go to noise reduction
到效果 我们就去降噪
and now since only noise is selected we
现在因为只选择了噪音 所以我们
can say get nose noise profile so when
可以说获取鼻子噪声配置文件的时候
we click this it'll get a profile adjust
我们点击此按钮 它将进行配置文件调整
this part to selective so we just we get
这部分是有选择性的 所以我们只是我们得到
it and it just goes away and doesn't say
它就这样消失了 没有说
anything but it's got it and it's
任何东西 但它得到了它 它是
remembered and recorded that now we can
记住并记录下来 现在我们可以
select everything so we can double click
选择所有内容 以便我们可以双击
or we can go
或者我们可以走了
control a to select everything and we
控件a来选择所有内容 然后我们
can go to effects and we can go to noise
可以去特效 我们可以去噪音
reduction again now we can work off of
再次减少 现在我们可以工作了
step two because it already has saved in
第二步 因为它已经保存在
its memory a nose profile of that noise
它记忆是噪音的鼻子侧影
and so now we can come in here and make
所以现在我们可以来到这里 让
some different adjustments so I've
一些不同的调整 所以我
already changed I think by default this
已经更改了 我认为默认情况下
was down at 12 for me so this might be
对我来说降到了12分 所以这可能是
your default so go to preview and I'll
您的默认设置 请转到预览 我将
just play back and you'll hear what it
只要回放一下 你就会听到它是什么
sounds like so that's better than it was
听起来比以前好多了
I think this is kind of how it was zero
我认为这就是为什么它是零
is kind of like your baseline but if we
有点像你的基线 但如果我们
if we bring this up to maybe 16 and do
如果我们把这个数字提高到16岁 然后
preview that sounds a lot better so we
预演听起来好多了 所以我们
can keep bringing this up and that noise
可以一直提着这个和那个声音
gets softer and softer one risk we have
变得越来越软是我们面临的一个风险
is we want to kind of make sure that
我们想要确保
it's not affecting the way our my voice
它不会影响我们的声音
sounds let's hit preview here and listen
声音 让我们在这里点击预览 然后听
that's actually pretty good so I'm just
这真的很好 所以我只是
gonna hit OK now and look it gets rid of
现在我要点击OK 看 它已经摆脱了
that noise so now if we go back to the
所以现在如果我们回到
beginning and play that's pretty good
开始和演奏 真的很好
it's a lot better than was before so
比以前好多了 所以
listen to this this is where our noise
听这个 这就是我们的噪音
was if we hit play now it's very quiet
如果我们现在按下播放 就会很安静
if I do control Z and play that we'll
如果我真的控制了Z 我们就会
see it's loud again so that is
看到它再次响亮 那就是
effectively using noise reduction you
有效地使用降噪功能
just have to get a noise profile first
我只需要先弄个噪音档案
we go to noise reduction and then while
我们去降噪 然后当
that selected get profile and then we go
选择了获取配置文件 然后我们开始
to select everything effects and apply
选择一切效果并应用
it so kind of two steps there kind of
它有两个步骤 有点
play with it and you know if you if you
玩它 你知道如果你
accidentally keep this part selected and
意外地保持此零件处于选中状态 并
you go to effects and we go to noise
你去特效 我们去噪音
reduction it will only do a noise
减少噪音只会产生噪音
reduction on that part of the selection
减少了选择的那部分
and everything else will still we see
而其他的一切我们仍将看到
this is still noise over here there's
这里还是很嘈杂 还有
still noise where I'm talking but this
我说话的地方仍然有噪音 但这个
is like quiet because our selection
就像是安静的因为我们的选择
wasn't made properly so just make sure
做得不好所以一定要确保
when you apply it you have everything
当你应用它 你拥有一切
selected and when you get the profile
当你得到配置文件时
you only
你只
the noise selected well that's what I
噪音选择得很好 这就是我
want to share with you just a quick
我想和你分享一下
quick introduction to the noise
快速介绍噪音
reduction tool hopefully you found this
还原工具希望你能找到这个
informative go ahead and like comment
信息继续前进 喜欢评论
subscribe and I'll catch you in the next
订阅 我将在下一个
video
视频